export const week1 = [
  {
    question: "Not much here pal",
    answer: "I said there's nothing!",
  },
  {
    question: "Not much to see here",
    answer: ":)",
  },
];

export const week2 = [
  {
    question: "What does action do in forms?",
    answer: "URL to use for form submission?",
  },
  {
    question: "What does method do in forms?",
    answer: "HTTP method to use for form submission",
  },
  {
    question: "What does enctype do in forms?",
    answer: "Encoding tpe to use for form submission",
  },
  {
    question: "What 11 elements can forms contain?",
    answer:
      "- <label> \n- <input>\n- <select>\n- <textarea>\n- <button>\n- <fieldset>\n- <legend>\n- <datalist>\n- <output>\n- <option>\n- <optgroup>",
  },
  {
    question: "What are 6 attributes that text input can have?",
    answer:
      "- Value: Shown as 'default' value in the text field\n- readonly: the value cannot be changed\n- size: visible width (sets the width of the input based on characters)\n- minlength: minimum number of characters allowed to be entered\n- maxlength: maximum number of characters allowed to be entered\n- placeholder: a short hint describing the expected value fo a text area",
  },
  {
    question: "What are 6 attributes that number input can have?",
    answer:
      "value: shown as 'default' value in the text field\n- readonly: the value cannot be changed\n- min: minimum value allowed to be entered\n- max: maxiumum value allowed to be entered\n- step: granularity that is expected (and required) of the value\n- placeholder: a short hint describing the expected value of a text area",
  },
  {
    question: "What does <optgroup> do?",
    answer:
      "The <optgroup> tag is used to group related options in the <select> element",
  },
  {
    question: "How many characters can textarea hold?",
    answer: "Textarea can hold unlimited characters.",
  },
];

export const week3 = [
  {
    question: "What are the benefits of semantic markup?",
    answer:
      "❑ Maintainability\n❑ Performance\n❑ Accessibility\n❑ Search engine optimization(SEO)",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the five principles of accessible web design?",
    answer:
      "The W3C created the Web Accessibility Initiative (WAI) in 1997 to improve the accessibility of websites. Perhaps the most important guidelines in that document are: \n❑ Use document structure (Semantic) tags: e.g., <article>, <strong> \n❑ Provide metadata: e.g., <html lang='en'> \n• Provide text alternatives for any nontext content so that it can be changed into other forms people need, such as large print, braille, speech, symbols, or simpler language. \n• Create content that can be presented in different ways (for example, simpler layout) without losing information or structure. \n• Provide ways to help users navigate, find content, and determine where they are.",
  },
  {
    question: "How to make tables accessible? (2)",
    answer:
      "❑ Describe the table’s content using the <caption> element \n❑ Connect the cells with a textual description in the header using use the scope attribute",
  },
  {
    question: "How to make forms accessible? (2)",
    answer:
      "❑ use of the <fieldset>, <legend>, and <label> elements. \n❑ Each <label> element should be associated with a single input element.",
  },
  {
    question: "Explain the relationship between selectors.",
    answer:
      "➢ Descendant selector(space” “)\n➢ Child selector (>)\n➢ Adjacent sibling selector(+)\n➢ General sibling selector(~)",
  },
];

export const week4 = [
  {
    question: "Nothing worth studying (for me)",
    answer: "Go check the slides",
  },
  {
    question: "Don't need to study this (you might)",
    answer: "Check the slides",
  },
];
export const week5 = [
  {
    question: "Why use Javascript?",
    answer:
      "• JavaScript does not need any environment setup \n• Popularity. \n• The early web browsers supported it as a lightweight and flexible way to add interactivity to pages",
  },
  {
    question: "What can Javascript do?",
    answer:
      "• Dynamically Update Content .\n• Manipulating HTML And CSS .\n• Animate Images And Content And Create Image Gallery .\n• Manipulate And Validate Data .\n• Control Multimedia [Audio, Video, Etc......] .\n• Web Browser Games .\n• Mobile Apps .",
  },
  {
    question: "What can't javascript do?",
    answer:
      "It can’t write data permanently to an existing file \nIt can’t access files on the server. \nIt can’t get data directly from a server database. \nIt can’t handle file uploads.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the history of Javascript?",
    answer:
      "Introduced by Netscape in 1996. \n❑ European Computer Manufacturers Association (ECMA), ECMAScript in 1997. \n❑ The Sixth Edition (or ES6) \n❑ The latest version of ECMAScript is ES14 or ES2023)",
  },
  {
    question: "How does interpreter work?",
    answer:
      "Interpreter translates just one statement of the program at a time into machine code.",
  },
  {
    question: "Javascript vs. Java differences?",
    answer:
      "• interpreted, not compiled\n• more relaxed syntax and rules\n• fewer and 'looser' data types\n• variables don't need to be declared\n• errors often silent (few exceptions)\n• key construct is the function rather than the class contained within a web pageand integrates with its HTML/CSS content\n",
  },
  {
    question: "What does alert() do?",
    answer: "Displays content within a pop-up box.",
  },
  {
    question: "What does prompt() do?",
    answer:
      "prompt() Displays a message and an input field within a model window.",
  },
  {
    question: "What does confirm() do?",
    answer:
      "Confirm() Displays a question in a modal window with ok and cancel buttons.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the three ways when Javascript code executes?",
    answer:
      "❑ Automatically when the page loads\n❑ When your script calls a function\n❑ In response to some event, such as the user clicking a button",
  },
  {
    question: "Are variables dynamic or static in Javascript?",
    answer: "Variables are dynamically typed in Javascript.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the scope of var?",
    answer: "Var declarations are function-scoped",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the scope of let?",
    answer: "let variables are block-scoped",
  },
  {
    question: "Can var variables be re-declared?",
    answer: "var variables can be updated and re-declared within the scope.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can let variables be re-declared?",
    answer: "Let variables can be updated, but not re-declared.",
  },
  {
    question: "Are var variables hoisted?",
    answer: "Var variables are hoisted with an initial value undefined.",
  },
  {
    question: "Are let variables hoisted?",
    answer: "let variables are not hoisted with an initial value.",
  },
];

export const week6 = [
  {
    question: "What is the DOM?",
    answer:
      "The document object model is created from the document's HTML. \nEach branch of the tree ends in a node, and each node contains objects. DOM methods allow programmatic access to the tree.",
  },
  {
    question: "What does each node have?",
    answer: "- Name of element\n- Attributes, and their values\n- Content",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the three type of DOM nodes?",
    answer: "- Element Nodes\n- Text Nodes\n- Attribute Nodes",
  },
  {
    question: "What are some basic node object properties? (8)",
    answer:
      "- childNodes\n- firstChild\n- lastCHild\n- nodeName\n- nodeType\n- nodeValue\n- parentNode\n- textContent",
  },
  {
    question: "What are 5 selection methods?",
    answer:
      "getElementById('id'), getElementsByClassName('name'), getElementsByTagName('name'), querySelector('selector'), and querySelectorAll(selector)",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you create a node?",
    answer: "document.createElement()",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the insertion and removal methods in the DOM? (5)",
    answer:
      "node.prepend(... nodes or string) - insert into node, at the beginning\n- node.before(...nodes or strings) - insert right before node\n- node.after(...nodes or strings) - insert right after node\n- node.append(...nodes or strings) to add the new nodes to the existing DOM tree\n- node.remove() - remove nodes",
  },
  {
    question: "What are some common DOM events?",
    answer:
      "- (Mouse Events) click, dblclick, mouseenter, mouseleave\n- (Keyboard Events) keypress, keydown, keyup\n- (Form Events) submit, change, focus, blur\n- (Document/Window Events) load, resize, scroll, unload",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the three kinds of errros in Javascript?",
    answer:
      "Syntax Errors: Occur when your code violates the fundamental rules (or syntax) of the language). \n- Runtime Errors: Occur when  avalid piece of code tries to do something that it's not allowed to do, or that is impossible\n- Logic Errors: OCcur when there are bugs in our code. And we don't get intended results from the script.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you error handle in Javascript?",
    answer:
      "• The try statement allows you to define a block of code to be tested for errors while it is being executed. \n• The catch statement allows you to define a block of code to be executed, if an error occurs in the try block.",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the throw statement do in Error Handling?",
    answer:
      "• The throw statement allows you to create a custom error. \n• The throw statement is written within the try block \n• The exception given can be a String, Number, Boolean or Object: \n1. Syntax for the throw statement \n \nfunction findSum(numbers, startIndex, endIndex) { \nif (startIndex < 0) { \nthrow 'startIndex is less than 0.'; \n} \nelse if (endIndex >= numbers.length) { \nthrow 'endIndex is too large.';",
  },
];

export const fullQuestionList = [
  ...week1,
  ...week2,
  ...week3,
  ...week4,
  ...week5,
  ...week6,
];
